Handler One to Undertaker.
Multiple enemy interceptor groups
at points 30 and 50.
Battalion-sized units
of Löwes and Grauwolfs.
All units, advance immediately
and take them out.
Though, with that many of them,
I bet you're all gonna die!
Go! Hurry!
Go, pigs!
Fight until you break, Eighty-Six!
What's this?
Hey, stop it!
Stop it! Stay away!
Shut up! Shut up!
May 13th, Stellar Year 2148
As you can see, it's another beautiful day today
in all 85 districts around the country!
Why not go out with your friends
and family today?
The weather will be a little worse tomorrow,
but you won't need an umbrella.
Have a great weekend, everyone!
Now for today's update on the war
from San Magnolia Military HQ!
The Legion mechanized infantry drones
belonging to the Giadian Empire
that invaded Combat District 17
took severe damage from our own
nation's unmanned combat units—
the Juggernauts—
and were forced to withdraw.
Damage taken by our side was minimal,
with no human injuries or fatalities!
Combat via highly advanced,
ethically responsible drones
has resulted in zero fatalities on our side!
The day when our nation's righteousness
finally smashes the evil remnants
of the wicked Empire is not far off!
Glory to the Republic of San Magnolia,
and to the five-color flag!
San Magnolia Military HQ
Morning, Major!
Those pigs sure were crying
their heads off yesterday.
It was a pretty crazy fight.
I bet at least five of them died.
Not that any people were on board!
Hey, everybody!
The doll-loving princess is glaring at us!
Why do you look so sad, Major Milizé?
It's just a few busted-up drones!
Listen, you—
Morning.
Morning, Annette.
You're up early. You normally sleep in.
I was up working all night.
Not like those morons.
Forget them!
This isn't the battlefield.
We're inside the Gran Mur.
And the enemy will be gone in two years.
If anything, you're the weirdo
for taking it seriously.
I just think this country's
conscience has—
Right, right.
I'm not awake enough
to listen to your speeches.
What's that Processor's problem?
He's just a part!
That's right!
We're from District 1. Why do we have to listen
to bitching from the pigs in District 86?
Why do you care so much
about the drones, Lena?
They're not drones.
I'll try again, then.
Why do you care so much about the Eighty-Six?
The battlefield calls, milady.
Initiate ID confirmation.
Major Vladilena Milizé.
Eastern Theater Forces, Combat District 9.
Defense Line 3 Unit Command
and Control Officer.
Activate Para-RAID.
Synchronization target: Pleiades Processor.
Synchronization complete.
Handler One to Pleiades:
Glad to be working with you today.
Pleiades to Handler One:
Synchronization channel clear.
Be careful.
The enemy's entering firing range.
Be careful—
Every time, you're so kind
to us inhuman Eighty-Six.
It's very sweet, human lady.
You're changing my assigned unit,
General Karlstahl?
Yes, one of the unit's Handlers
is retiring from his post.
As such, a new one is needed immediately.
If they can't leave their post
until a successor is decided,
does that mean it's a unit
defending an important base?
Yes, Defense Line 1 in
Eastern Defense Line Combat District 1.
AKA the Spearhead Squadron.
It's comprised of veterans
from all across the eastern theater.
An ace unit, you could say.
But...
I'm a new major.
I don't think I could handle it.
And you're also the youngest person ever
to make it to the post of major.
If you try to be too humble,
you'll make unnecessary enemies, Lena.
I'm sorry, Uncle Jérôme.
I'm sure Václav would be proud
if he could see his daughter, too.
How is Margareta?
The same as ever. She won't stop
telling me to get married.
I'm sure.
Actually, we can't find anyone
willing to take on the role.
They're an ace unit, right?
Wouldn't it be an honor for any
Republic soldier to command them?
Yes, that's true for the unit itself.
Its commander unit's name: Undertaker.
There's a story behind it.
A story?
They call it the Reaper.
It destroys any Handler
who tries to take it.
The Processor destroys the Handler?
Not the other way around?
Correct.
It's not just a ghost story?
I don't have time in my schedule
to share ghost stories with my subordinates.
Almost all Handlers for the unit with Undertaker
in them request to retire or change units.
Some have even committed suicide.
It's hard to believe,
but they say they're haunted
by the "voices of the dead."
The dead?
You're free to refuse, Lena.
You work too hard, anyway.
A Handler's job is to monitor the unit,
keep their commands to a minimum,
and let the local commander take control.
I'll do it.
I'll give my all to managing Spearhead
and being its Command and Control Officer.
You don't need to do more than your job.
Stop trying to interact with the Processors.
It's a commander's job to know her men.
Well, while I'm lecturing you,
let me add one more thing.
Stop putting the number of fatalities
in your reports.
Officially, there are no humans
on the battlefield.
So there are no fatalities.
That doesn't mean we can ignore them.
What we're doing shouldn't even be allowed.
Lena.
You really are just like Václav.
All right.
I appoint you, Vladilena Milizé, Handler—
that is, Command and Control Officer—
for Defense Line Combat District 1,
Defense Line 1.
Have the paperwork done
by the time you get there.
And do your best.
I'll do my best until my final mission.
And you accepted it?
Republic of San Magnolia Military Research Wing
Sheesh...
You're such a weirdo.
It's an honor to be put in charge
of an ace unit.
And it's an important job.
And that stuff about it destroying Handlers
is all lies, right?
I bet they all just don't care about their jobs,
so they lied to get out of it.
It's true that some committed suicide.
One of Spearhead's Handlers went crazy
and blew his own head off with a shotgun.
OK, exam's done. No problems, as usual.
Thanks for your cooperation.
But why commit suicide?
We got a request to look into it.
They thought it might be a problem
with the Para-RAID.
Quitting isn't a big deal,
but a suicide needs to be looked into.
And?
Dunno.
You don't know?
The Handler was dead.
How we were supposed to investigate it?
You're the leader of the development team.
Is that really okay?
We did our jobs.
There was nothing wrong
with the RAID Device. End of story.
We told them that if they wanted to know more,
they'd have to bring us the Undertaker.
But those idiots in transport said,
"This flight has no seats open for pigs!"
Then you didn't talk to Undertaker?
We just read the report.
"No idea," they said.
We told them about the dead Handler,
and all they said was, "I see."
Well, they're an Eighty-Six.
It's not outside the realm of possibility
that a Para-RAID could cause insanity.
You're putting extra pressure
on part of the brain to allow it
to share sensory data
with a completely different person.
And we use it only to share hearing.
If you tried to synchronize vision as well,
it would burn out your brain.
Too much load on the brain,
and you don't come back.
Using the Para-RAID
means accepting those risks.
But your father was one of the authorities
in this field of research.
The fundamental principles
were all developed by someone else.
There's a lot I don't know, actually.
Listen, Lena, you should join us in R&D.
The military's just a jobs program right now.
When the Legion are gone in two years,
"former military" isn't going
to mean a thing on your résumé.
Thanks.
But it's wartime right now.
Those Processors are crazy!
You don't know what will happen
with the Para-RAIDs.
The Eighty-Six die quickly anyway,
so it doesn't matter.
But I don't want that for you.
But, still, it's cowardly.
Right, right.
You really are weird.
I changed the settings.
Thanks.
Oh, Lena! I made chiffon cake.
Want some?
Hm... I'll pass today.
I'll see you later.
I used real eggs.
And real milk.
It's so good!
How's it feel to actually eat
the real thing for once?
Wonderful!
But part of me wonders
if this is how it really tasted.
You forget when you eat only artificial stuff.
I've got cream puffs, too.
They don't taste like cheese
when they don't have cheese in them,
or look like they're about
to spit out black smoke, right?
Are you talking about the cream puffs
I made last time?
It'll be fine, this time!
I gave some to a potential marriage partner
yesterday, and he cried tears of joy.
Sounds like you got a good match for once.
He must've really loved it.
Of course!
I added a card with a lipstick kiss
and the words, "To My Beloved."
I dropped them both in the mailbox of the place
where he lives with his mistress.
May 20th, Stellar Year 2148
What's wrong, Pleiades?
Come in!
What's wrong?
Handler One to Pleiades!
Stop...
He's dead!
Evasive maneuvers!
Damn it!
Handler One to all members of Squadron 3.
The enemy unit has begun its retreat.
Squadron 4 will take over
the patrol mission.
Return to base.
Roger.
Pleiades and the other six who died...
I'm so sorry about them.
As always, thank you
for your kind words, Handler One.
Just so you're aware,
Squadron 3 will be re-formed
with a new Handler.
Thank you for everything.
I'm going to be the Command
and Control Officer for Spearhead.
That's great news.
You have my deepest sympathies, Handler One.
What does that mean—
Say hello to the Reaper for me.
May 22nd, Stellar Year 2148
Para-RAID, activate.
Synchronization target:
Spearhead Processor.
May 12th, Stellar Year 2148
Nice, man!
Get cleaning.
They're having a good time over there, huh?
Wait! Wait!
Eggs!
Welcome back.
Huh?
Hey, help me!
Coming.
And, done!
Hey, have fun out there today.
You mean, "Have fun out there, sir."
Members of Spearhead, it's breakfast time!
Gather round!
Right, right.
Coming, coming.
Morning! Morning!
Morning.
Let's eat!
There are more omelets.
Gimme more!
Calm down.
Can't you chew your food?
Is it good, Kuro?
Right.
Hey, our Handler went crazy, right?
The one in the battle yesterday.
That one's not coming back.
I heard it.
"Stay away! Hey, stop!"
Stop it, guys.
White Pig always does that.
Whoever comes next,
the same thing will happen.
Right?
But everybody was able
to go yesterday, right, Shin?
Yeah. It's fine.
Well, if we're going to die,
we'd rather have our Reaper guide us.
What?
Here.
May 22nd, Stellar Year 2148
It hurts...
Damn it all!
Damn it!
I don't want to die.
Shin...
Promise me...
Don't forget...
Was Kujo able to go?
Yeah.
What about Brother's voice?
No.
I see.
There's none left.
You suck.
I win!
Handler One to all Spearhead units.
Greetings. I am your new
Command and Control officer.
A woman?
I've contacted you tonight
to introduce myself.
Hello, Handler One.
This is Spearhead Squadron's
combat commander,
Personal Name: Undertaker.
We've received word of a new Handler coming.
We look forward to working with you.
As do I.
Nice to meet you, Undertaker.
Spearhead.